TYLER KOTLOWSKI

SKILLS

I am a Researcher foremost, Data Analyst, Django Framework, Web Developer and Python Programmer. I've learned many skills, trades, and practices. I am useful in many areas to provide upmost efficiency to those around me. I am a great team member and leader.

EXPERIENCE

LOASM Technician | USAF | 2012 - 2014

Worked on F-22 stealth aircraft structures for the Air Force.

FG Welder | Relco | 2014

Welded food grade stainless steel for dairy manufacturing companies throughout United States.

Electrician | Friendship Homes | 2014 – 2015

Setup raw wiring in mobile homes, including, light fixtures, appliances, circuitry, and other electrical component installations.

Insurance Agent | Independent | 2015 – 2016

Worked primarily with supplemental insurance and partly with major health plans. Worked with the design/sales of a new insurance platform tool (Everrest)

Programmer | 2016-Present

Github - https://github.com/Nanonzt

Portfolio - http://Kotlowski.graphics

Trading Analyst | Advisor | 2017-PRESENT

OBJECTIVE

Why hire me? Because I can do many things. I have learned many traits, skills, tools, and knowledge to be incredibly effective at all that I do. If I don't have the answer, I'll find it. I look for patterns, rhythms, series of things, to create more effective paths of execution.





Best Method kotlowski.graphics @ gmail com Work (320) 429 0480

VOLUNTEERING

I've done environmental clean up in most cities I have lived in. I have volunteered time as security for multiple festivals in Alaska for USAF promotion purposes.

I am a USAF Active Duty Veteran.
I am also an ambassador/advisor
to multiple cryptocurrency
projects.

EDUCATION | STUDY

HS Diploma | 2012 | YME

LOASM Cert | 2013 | USAF

Health and Accident Insurance License | 2015

Python | 2016-2017 | Florida Institute of Technology

Python 3 | 2018 | Bootcamp

Django 2 | 2018 | Bootcamp

Languages

HTML5

CSS4

JavaScript

Bootstrap 3

Java

R

Other Skills

Linux, Unix, Server Administration, Unity 3D

PROGRAMMING // PROJECTS

--Clide--

Al Personal Assistant

--Sal--

Automated File Merging Program

--Global Ocean Pollution Research--

Working with R and Unity to produce a real-time animation of the oceans plastic pollution.

(Development)

--Cryptobot--

Bitcoin trade-bot, automates off my personal trade habits. (Testing)

INTERESTS

Building Python Bots.

I research cryptocurrency projects and technology.

Time with my wife and kids.

I learn new skills.

GOALS

To live a life of knowledge.

Contribute to great projects.

To retire earlier than most.

REFERENCES

Adam Savariego

Long Time Friend / Advisor (320) 226-5082

Jerry Streitz

Advisor (320) 761-3106

Carlos Esquibel

Long Time Friend (320) 226-8358